Guide to the Clark, Hall, and Peck and White Brothers Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- White Brothers, 1880s-1982; Series I
  - New Haven
    - Plot map book for Fair Haven addresses (Box 387)
      - Map (District) 129
        - Plots 1-60 (Box 411)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Blatchley Avenue, Clay Street, Fillmore Street, Grand Avenue, Haven Street, James Avenue, Lloyd Street, Maltby Street, Market Street, Monroe Street, Pine Street, Popular Street, Shelter Street.
        - Plots 61-120 (Box 412)
        - Plots 121-180 (Box 413)
        - Plots 181-240 (Box 414)
        - Plots 241-279 (Box 415)
      - Map (District) 130
        - Plots 1-40 (Box 416)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Atwater Street, Bright Street, Clay Street, Clinton Avenue, Ferry Street, Grand Avenue, Pine Street, Poplar Street.
        - Plots 41-80 (Box 417)
        - Plots 81-127 (Box 418)
      - Map (District) 131
        - Plots 1-40 (Box 419)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Clinton Avenue, Grand Avenue, Grannis Street, Lewis Street, North Front Street, Perkins Street, Pine Street.
        - Plots 41-81 (Box 420)
      - Map (District) 132
        - Plots 1-25 (Box 421)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Chapel Street, Grand Avenue, Haven Street, James Street, Mill Street, Saltonstall Avenue, Wollcott Street.
        - Plots 26-67 (Box 422)
      - Map (District) 133
        - Plots 1-50 (Box 423)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Blatchley Avenue, Chapel Street, Exchange Street, Grand Avenue, James Street, Lloyd Street, Saltonstall Avenue, Wolcott Street, Woolsey Street.
        - Plots 51-100 (Box 424)
        - Plots 101-150 (Box 425)
        - Plots 151-200 (Box 426)
        - Plots 201-260 (Box 427)
      - Map (District) 134
        - Plots 1-60 (Box 428)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Blatchley Avenue, Chapel Street, Exchange Street, Ferry Street, Grand Avenue, Poplar Street, Richard Street, Saltonstall Avenue, Wolcott Street, Woolsey Avenue.
        - Plots 61-120 (Box 429)
        - Plots 121-170 (Box 430)
        - Plots 171-219 (Box 431)
      - Map (District) 135
        - Plots 1-50 (Box 432)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Chambers Street, Chapel Street, East Pearl Street, Exchange Street, Ferry Street, Grand Avenue, Houston Street, Pierpont Street.
        - Plots 51-100 (Box 433)
        - Plots 101-146 (Box 434)
      - Map (District) 136
        - Plots 1-25 (Box 435)
          Includes abstracts of title for properties on Chambers Street, East Pearl Street, Exchange Street, Grand Avenue, Pierpont Street, South Front Street, Talmadge Street.
        - Plots 26-68 (Box 436)
      - Map (District) 137, Plots 1-26 (Box 437)
        Includes of abstracts of title for properties on Chapel Street, James Street, Lloyd Street, River Street.
      - Map (District) 138, Plots 1-19 (Box 438)
        Includes of abstracts of title for properties on Chapel Street, Ferry Street, River Street.
      - Map (District) 139, Plots 1-18 (Box 438)
        Includes abstracts of title for properties on East Pearl Street, Houston Street, River Street, South Front Street.
    - Flat files (alphabetical) by street, property owner, realty company, or name of development
      - Beaver Hills Co. (Box 439)
      - "Beaver Parks Estates" (Box 439)
      - Belle Dock, 2 (Box 439)
      - "Bennan's Job" (Properties on Chapel and Franklin Sts.) (Box 439)
      - Bishop Ridge (Map of) (Box 439)
      - Blahester Quarry (Box 440)
      - Boulevard (Industrial Park) (Box 440)
      - Boulevard (New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad properties) (Box 440)
      - E. Burr Street (Box 440)
      - 234 Church Street (Gold Building CONALCO) (Box 440)
      - Cimino Building Co., Inc. (Box 440)
      - Cimino, Rose (Box 441)
      - Coliseum (Box 441)
      - Community Health Care Center (Box 441)
      - Crosby Realty Company Inc. (Land in New Haven and East Haven) (Box 441)
      - "Dell Acres" (Box 441)
      - "Edgewood" (Map of) (Box 442)
      - Extension of Elaine Terrace (Box 442)
      - Fairmont Avenue (Box 442)
      - Geisenger Realty Co. (Properties on Ferry and Haven Street) (Box 442)
      - Heller, Anne (Properties on Asylum Street, Carlisle Street, Clover Place and Truman Street) (Box 442)
      - Hemingway Terrace (Box 442)
      - "Highview"Development (Box 442)
      - Kautz (786 Chapel Street) (Box 442)
      - Kormarc Incorporated (Box 442)
      - Lakewood (Box 442)
      - Long Hill Terrace (Box 442)
      - Long Wharf (Box 442)
      - "Majestic Laundry Co."(Land owned by) (Box 442)
      - New Haven, City of (Land owned by) (Box 443)
      - New Haven Food Co-op Inc. (Box 443)
      - New Haven Terminal Incorporated (Box 443)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad (Box 443)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad (Property of an old freight warehouse of the Derby Railroad) (Box 443)
      - "Oak Hill" (Box 443)
      - "Oak Ridge Inc." (Box 443)
      - "Ortnese Incorporated" (Box 443)
      - Parcel Post Building (New on Brewery Street) (Box 444)
      - "Proposed Postal Facility"adjoining Brewery Street Post Office (Box 444)
      - Pond Lily (Box 444)
      - Prospect Gardens Condominiums Inc., 1000 Quinnipiac Ave (Nine acres at the rear of property), "Quinnipiac Gardens,""Recreation Park,"Register Publishing Company, "Riverside Park,""Robinwood,"Roger White Drive (Box 445)
      - 1000 Quinnipiac Avenue (Nine acres at the rear of property) (Box 445)
      - "Quinnipiac Gardens" (Box 445)
      - "Recreation Park" (Box 445)
      - Register Publishing Company (Box 445)
      - "Riverside Park" (Box 445)
      - "Robinwood" (Box 445)
      - Roger White Drive (Box 445)
      - Senrad Company (Box 446)
      - "Shartenberg's Block"(Land owned by the city of New Haven) (Box 446)
      - "Sheff Garage" (Box 446)
      - Sopet, Dick (Box 446)
      - Springside (Box 446)
      - Stiles Realty Co. (Box 446)
      - Summit Street (Box 446)
      - Taft Hotel and Taft Annex (Box 447)
      - Three Judges Motel Inc. (Box 447)
      - Three Judges Restaurant (Box 447)
      - Townsend Farm (Box 447)
      - Trap Rock Co. (Box 448)
      - United States Post Office (Church Street) (Box 448)
      - Upson Terrace (Box 448)
      - Village Condominium (Box 448)
      - "West Hills"Development (Box 448)
      - West Rock (Box 448)
      - Whalley Center Blvd. (Box 449)
      - Whitney, Henrietta E. (Estate) (Box 449)
      - Yale Golf Course (Box 449)
      - Yale-New Haven Hospital (Box 449)
    - Flat files (non-alphabetical)
      - Yale-New Haven Hospital: Grace-New Haven Hospital (Box 450)
      - New Haven Marine Construction Co. (Box 450)
      - Trustees for the Grammar School of New Haven or Hopkins Committee (Box 450)
      - Grantee deeds of the Collegiate School, Yale College, Hopkins Grammar School (Box 450)
      - Grantor deeds of the Collegiate School, Yale College, Hopkins Grammar School (Box 450)
      - Correspondence relating to Wilson & Co. (Bond issue), 1935 July 15 (Box 450)
      - Winchester Repeating Arms Co. (Forbes Avenue and Water Street) (Box 451)
      - Includes files entitled 1094 Whalley Avenue (Box 452)
      - "37 acres of land Fitch Street, State of Connecticut new site Teachers' College" (Box 452)
        General note
        The site is now occupied by Southern Connecticut State University.
      - Estate of Nicholas W. Hubinger of New Haven (Box 452)
      - Grantor-grantee deed Dyer and Henry White (Box 452)
      - Oliver F. Winchester grantor-grantee (Box 452)
      - George Hults alias Hultze grantor and grantee (Box 452)
      - "Globe Building" (Chapel Street and Church Street) (Box 452)
      - IZZO (Box 453)
      - "Reuse parcel B-6-B" (N. Grand Avenue) (Box 453)
      - "Reuse parcel B-12-0" (N. Fair Street and W. Union Street) (Box 453)
      - "Reuse parcel S-7-A" (S. George Street and N. Dwight Street) (Box 453)
      - "Wooster Square parcel B-12-A" (Olive Street and Union Street) (Box 453)
      - "Wooster Square parcel B-12-F" (Fair Street and Olive Street) (Box 453)
      - "Wooster Square parcel B-12-G" (Olive Street) (Box 453)
      - "Wooster Square parcel B-12-H" (Fair Street) (Box 453)
      - "Reuse parcel" C-1-P (Wallace Street and East Street) (Box 453)
      - Wooster Square (East Street) (Box 454)
      - Dixwell Avenue renewal (Box 454)
      - "New Haven reuse parcel D-2" (SNET N. Court Street, E. State Street, and S. Pitkin Street) (Box 454)
      - Oak Street Connector (Block J, parcels 1-21) (Box 454)
      - Land disposition and rehabilitation agreement, City of New Haven, New Haven Redevelopment Agency, reuse parcel S-18 Fair Haven Renewal and Redevelopment area (Box 454)
      - Land disposition and rehabilitation agreement, City of New Haven, New Haven Redevelopment Corporation, and Community Realty Co., reuse parcel C-7-H (441-445 Chapel Street, Wooster Square) (Box 455)
      - Land disposition and rehabilitation agreement, City of New Haven, New Haven Redevelopment Corporation, and Richard K. and Marianne Mazan, reuse parcel S-36 (613 Chapel Street, Wooster Square) (Box 455)
      - Land disposition and rehabilitation agreement, City of New Haven, New Haven Redevelopment Corporation, and Iglesia Pentecostal Puerta de Salvacion Inc., reuse parcel S-20 (Hill Renewal and Redevelopment) (Box 455)
      - Land disposition and rehabilitation agreement, City of New Haven, New Haven Redevelopment Corporation, and M. Edgar and Cornelia H. Rosenblum, reuse parcel S-37 (621 Chapel Street) (Box 455)
      - Land disposition and rehabilitation agreement, City of New Haven, New Haven Redevelopment Corporation, and Michael and Genevieve Farmerson, reuse parcel C-1 Fair Haven Renewal and Redevelopment area, Fair Haven Project Area Committee Inc. (James Street) (Box 455)
      - "Cutler Corner"(866-868 Chapel Street) (Box 456)
      - The Powell Building (151-159 Church Street and 173 Court Street) (Box 456)
      - Commonwealth Land Title Insurance Co. (Orange Street, corner of George Street) (Box 457)
      - Railroad information, New York, New Haven-Hartford Railroad (Box 457)
        Mortgage information in Secretary of State's office.
      - Abstract of title for 426 Prospect Street (Box 458)
      - "West Hills" (Valley Street) (Box 458)
        Contains dates, maps and correspondence.
      - "West Hills" (Valley Street) (Box 458)
        Contains abstract of title only.
      - National Wire Corporation abstracts of title (Wheeler Street, Ferry Street, Fairmont Avenue), 2 (Box 459)
      - Abstract of title for Geisinger Realty Inc. (130-138 Haven Street) (Box 459)
      - Abstract of title for Swift & Co. (Long Wharf) (Box 460)
      - Abstract of title for 84 Howe Street (Box 461)
      - Abstract of title for 60 Fitch Street and 202 Orange Street (West Haven) (Box 461)
      - Abstract of title for 323 Columbus Avenue (N. W. corner of Derby Avenue and Forest Road), 1495-1499 Boulevard, 146-150 Everit Street, 594-600 Prospect Street) (Box 461)
      - Abstract of title for Wire Rope Corporation, Volume I (Congress Avenue, Howard Avenue, and Daggett Street) (Box 462)
      - Abstract of title for Wire Rope Corporation, Volume II (Congress Avenue, Howard Avenue, and Daggett Street) "The Wire Rope Corporation" (W. Daggett Street, N. Congress Avenue and E. Howard Avenue) (Box 463)
      - "The Wire Rope Corporation"(W. Daggett Street, N. Congress Avenue and E. Howard Avenue) (Box 463)
      - Abstract of title for 81-83 Church Street (Corner of Center Street) (Box 464)
      - Abstract of title for 17 Howe Street, 70 Howe Street, 60-62 Church Street, and 791-795 Chapel Street (Box 464)
      - Abstract of title for 866-868 Chapel Street (S.E. corner of Church Street and Chapel Street) (Box 464)
      - 307-313 Street Ronan Street and 438-446 Whitney Avenue (Box 464)
      - Abstract of title for 100-102 Howe Street, Y. M. C. A. of New Haven, 52 Howe Street (Box 465)
      - Abstract of title for 482-484 Whitney Avenue, 486-492 Whitney Avenue, and 226-234 Ellsworth Avenue (Box 465)
      - Abstract of title for 23-31 Dwight Street, 315 Whitney Avenue, 260-262 York Street, 655 Ellsworth Avenue (Box 466)
      - Abstract of title for 81-83 Church Street (Box 466)
      - Abstract of title for 85-89 Church Street, 1171-1179 Chapel Street, 197 Park Street and 9 Howe Street (Box 466)
    - Project Files
      - Dixwell-Whalley Avenue (Public Housing)
        - Abstracts of title for properties on Whalley Avenue, Dixwell Avenue, Goffe Street, Bristol Street, Ashmun Street, Lake Place (Box 467)
        - Abstracts of title for properties on Dixwell Avenue, Lake Place, Ashmun Street, Bristol Street, Canal Street, Mansfield Street, Prospect Place, Lock Street (Box 468)
      - Interstate 91
        - Abstracts of title for properties on Chapel Street, Franklin Street, Street Johns Street, William Street, Chestnut Street, Grand Avenue, Bradley Street (Box 469)
        - Abstracts of title for properties on Franklin Street, William Street, Madison Street, State Street, Pulaski Street (formerly Sumner Street), Leonard Street, and Osborn Street (Box 470)
        - Abstracts of title for properties on Bradley Street, Trumbull Street, and Orange Street (Box 471)
        - Abstracts of title for properties on State Street, Wallace Street, Summer Street, Summer Place, Hamilton Street, Humphrey Street, and Franklin Street (Box 472)
        - Abstracts of title for properties on Mill River Street, Beach Street, and East Street (Box 473)
        - Abstracts of title for properties on Cedar Hill Avenue, Willow Street, View Street, and State Street (Box 474)
        - Abstracts of title for properties on State Street, Ferry Street, Cedar Hill Avenue, Bailey Street, Clinton Avenue, and View Street (Box 475)
        - Abstracts of title for properties on Bailey Street, Dover Street, Atwater Street, Rowe Street, Middletown Avenue, Park Place, Clinton Avenue, Wilcox Place, Mill River Street, and North Haven (Box 476)
        - Abstracts of title and easement maps for I-91 properties on Front Street in New Haven through North Haven (Box 477)
      - Oak Street Connector
        - Abstracts of title for properties on George Street, State Street, Whiting Street, Meadow Street, S. Orange Street, and Fair Street (Box 478)
        - Abstracts of title for properties on Wooster Street, Olive Street, Union Street, and Fair Street (Box 479)
        - Abstracts of title for properties on Wooster Street, Prindle Street, Fair Street, and Olive Street (Box 480)
        - Abstracts of title for properties on Chestnut Street, Water Street, Brown Street, Wooster Street, Brewery Street, and Warren Street (Box 481)
      - Tontine Hotel and Yale Bowl (Box 482)
  - Other Connecticut cities and towns
    - Ansonia
      - Index card locator file (Box 483)
      - Abstracts of title, 1-87 (Box 484)
      - Flat files
        - 3, 9, 10, 23, 30 (Box 484A)
        - 38, 39, 40, 45, 47, 52, 53, 55, 62, 64, 68, 79 (Box 484B)
      - Unnumbered flat file, "Mountain View Estates" (Box 484B)
    - Beacon Falls
      - Abstracts of title (Box 485)
      - Flat file (Box 485)
    - Berlin, Abstract of title (Box 485)
    - Bethany
      - Index card locator file (Box 486)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-45 (Box 487)
        - 46-100 (Box 488)
        - 101-145 (Box 489)
        - 146-195 (Box 490)
        - 196-251 (Box 491)
      - Flat files
        - 84, 88, 94, 105, 107, 127, 129, 161, 165, 182, 186, 192, 211, 212, 217, 224 (Box 492)
    - Branford
      - Index card locator file (Box 493)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-55 (Box 494)
        - 56-100 (Box 495)
        - 101-175 (Box 496)
        - 176-240 (Box 497)
        - 241-300 (Box 498)
        - 301-365 (Box 499)
        - 366-434 (Box 500)
        - 435-500 (Box 501)
        - 501-560 (Box 502)
        - 561-630 (Box 503)
        - 631-694 (Box 504)
        - 695-770 (Box 505)
        - Branford miscellaneous records (Box 506)
      - Flat files
        - 66, 74, 140, 143, 149, 151, 158, 164, 199, 220, 243, 244, 246 (Box 507)
        - 261A, 285, 301, 310, 326, 328, 339, 341, 352, 353, 363 (Box 508)
        - 373, 374, 379, 387, 402, 408, 432, 445, 466, 467, 470, 474, 478 (Box 509)
        - 500, 527, 533, 544, 559, 561, 566, 591, 601, 603, 635, 651 (Box 510)
        - 654, 658, 679, 689-690 (Box 511)
      - Unnumbered flat files
        - "Cherry Hill Farm" (Box 511)
        - "Land of heirs of Foote" (Box 511)
        - "Map of Chase Real Estate Inc." (Box 511)
    - Bridgeport
      - Abstracts of title (Box 512)
      - Flat files (Box 512)
    - Bristol
      - Abstract of title (Box 513)
      - Flat file (Box 513)
    - Brookfield abstracts of title (Box 513)
    - Chatham abstract of title (Box 513)
    - Cheshire
      - Index card locator file (Box 514)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-50 (Box 515)
        - 51-110 (Box 516)
        - 111-165 (Box 517)
        - 166-240 (Box 518)
        - 241-304 (Box 519)
        - 305-370 (Box 520)
        - 371-450 (Box 521)
        - 451-530 (Box 522)
        - 531-596, Cheshire miscellaneous records (Box 523)
      - Flat files
        - 84, 102, 105-106, 123, 155, 156, 157 (Box 524)
        - 190, 201, 202, 204, 218, 225, 227, 239, 278, 279, 286, 298 (Box 525)
        - 349, 375, 378, 391, 400, 411, 431, 432, 438, 457, 507, 531 (Box 526)
    - Chester
      - Abstracts of title (Box 527)
      - Flat file (Box 527)
    - Clinton
      - Index card locator file (Box 528)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-50 (Box 529)
        - 51-119, Clinton miscellaneous records (Box 530)
      - Flat files
        - 11-12-13, 21, 65, 72 (Box 531)
      - Unnumbered flat files, Clintonworth-Celanese (Box 531)
    - Danbury abstract of title (Box 532)
    - Darien abstract of title (Box 532)
    - Deep River
      - Abstracts of title (Box 532)
      - Flat files (Box 532)
    - Derby
      - Index card locator file (Box 533)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-60 (Box 534)
        - 61-108, Derby miscellaneous records (Box 535)
      - Flat files, 3, 4, 27, 47, 67, 69, 73 (Box 536A)
      - Unnumbered flat files
        - Clair H. Alling, born May 27, 1887 Susie A. Baldwin also of age 250 Main Street, Derby, Conn.-- Sept. 1926 (Box 536B)
        - "Theater Block" (Box 536B)
    - Durham
      - Index card locator file (Box 536)
      - Abstracts of title (Box 537)
      - Flat files (Box 538)
    - East Haddam abstract of title (Box 539)
    - East Haven
      - Abstracts of title
        - Admiral Street, Allen Court, Alpine Drive, Andover Street, Ann Street, Arden Street, Arthur Court, Arthur Road, Atwater Street, N. Atwater Street, Augur Road, Austin Avenue, "Baldwin Park"(High Street), Barberry Street, Barker Street, Bartlett Road, Batt Lane, Beach Avenue, Beatrice Drive, Beatson Avenue, Bellman Street, Bennett Road, Birger Street, Bishop Street, Borrmann Road, Boston Avenue, Boughton Place (Box 539)
        - Boxford Street, Bradford Avenue, Bradley Avenue, Bradley Street, "Bradford Manor,"Branhaven Drive, Brazos Road, Brennan Street, Bretton Street, Brockett Place, Brookfield Road, Browns Road, Burgess Street (Box 540)
        - "Bradley Park" (Main Street), "Bradley Park Ext."(Main Street), Burr Street, "Burr Street Terrace," Cambridge Court, "Campania Place"(Salerno Avenue), Canna Drive, Carlson Place, Carmen Street, Carol Drive, Caroline Road, Cass Street, Catherine Street, Cecelia Drive, Center Avenue, Center Street, Charles Drive, Charnes Drive (Box 541)
        - Charter Oak Avenue, Cherry Street, Chester Place, Chidsey Avenue, Church Street, Clancy Street, Clark Avenue, Clearview Avenue, Cliff Street, Clintonville Road, "Coe Estates," Cold Spring Avenue, Columbus Avenue, Congress Street, Coolidge Street, Corbin Road, Cortina Road, Cross Street, Dakota Street (Box 542)
        - Coe Avenue (Box 543)
        - Cosey Beach Avenue, Cosey Beach Avenue Ext., "Columbia Gardens" (South Main Street), "Cosey Beach Plat" (Coe Avenue), "Cosey Beach Plat No. 3" (Coe Avenue), "Cosey Beach Plat No. 4" (Coe Avenue), "Cosey Beach Plat Annex" (Silver Sands Road), "Cosey Beach Terrace" (Silver Sands Road) (Box 544)
        - Cosey Beach Road, Cox Drive, Crest Avenue (Box 545)
        - Dale Place, Dale Street, Damen Drive, David Drive, David Drive Ext., Deborah Drive, Deborah Lane, Deerfield Street, Dell Drive, Demeter Drive, Dewey Avenue, Diana Road, Diaz Street (Box 546)
        - Dodge Avenue, "Dodge Avenue Gardens," Donald Street, Dora Drive, Doran Street, Dorian Drive, Duncan Street, Duval Street, Dwight Place, Dyke Street, Edgar Street, Edgehill Drive (Box 547)
        - Edgemere Road, Edward Street, Eldred Drive, Ellen Place, Ellis Road, Elm Court, Elm Court Ext., Elm Street, Emma Road, Englewood Drive, Ericson Street, Estelle Road, "East Haven Gardens"Nos. 1, 2, 3 (Silver Sands Road), "Elvire Park" (Hill Street), "Fairlawn Terrace," "Fairmont Park" (Mansfield Grove Road), "Fairview Terrace,"Farm River Estates, Farm River Road, Far View Avenue, Farrell Avenue, Ferraro Drive, First Avenue, First Street, Fisco Drive (Box 548)
        - Florence Street, Foote Road, Forbes Place, Forest Street, Forest Road, Francis Street, Francis Street Ext., Frank Street, French Avenue (Box 549)
        - Foxon Boulevard, Foxon Hill Road (Box 550)
        - Foxon Road (Route 80) (Box 551)
        - Foxon Road (Route 80), Old Foxon Road (Box 552)
        - Frontage Road (East and West), Gabriel Street, Garry Drive, Gay Street, Gay Road, Gene Street, Gennessee Street, George Street, Gerald Street, Gerrish Place, Getty Road, Glen Haven Road, Glenmoor Drive, Gloria Place, Goodsell Road, Gordon Street (Box 553)
        - Gay Street, Grace Street, Grannis Street, Grant Road, Green Street, Green Glen Terrace, "Greenlawn Manor,""Green Lawn Park" (Hemingway Avenue), Griswold Street, Grove Street, Guilford Court, Gurney Street, Gustav Street, Hains Street, Half Mile Road, Hamilton Avenue, Hampton Road, Harmac Drive, Harrington Avenue, Hartmann Avenue, Harwich Street, "Hasson Lots" (Cosey Beach Avenue) (Box 554)
        - Hellstorm Road (Box 555)
        - Hemingway Avenue, "Hemingway Terrace" (Box 556)
        - Henry Street, Highland Avenue, Highland Drive, Highland Street (Box 557)
        - High Street, North High Street (West side?) (Box 558)
        - High Street, North High Street (East side?) (Box 559)
        - Hilda Street, Hill Street, "Hill Crest" (Bradley Avenue), Hilltop Road, Hilton Avenue, "Homewood Heights" (Laurel Street), Hobson Avenue (Smith Manor), Holland Road, Holmes Street, Hotchkiss Road, Hotchkiss Road Ext., Howe Court, Hudson Street (Box 560)
        - Hughes Street, Humbert Street, Hunt Lane, Hurlburt Drive, Hurley Road (Box 561)
        - Iver Avenue, Jamaica Court, James Road, James Street, Jane Court, Jardin Drive, "Jay Development Co." (Thompson Avenue), Jeffrey Road, Jillson Drive, Joan Court, Joffre Street, John Street (Box 562)
        - Joyce Road, Judith Lane, Julius Drive, Karen Way, Kenneth Street, Kenny Court, Kimberly Avenue, Kirkham Avenue, Kirkham Avenue Ext., Kossuth Street, Landing Place, "Lawn Crest" (Main Street), Laura Lane (Box 563)
        - Laurel Street (Box 564)
        - Ledyard Place, Lenox Street, Leonard Street, Liberty Place, Liberty Street, Library Place, Lincoln Street, Lindberg Street, Lucy Street,LynnCourt, Lynwood Place, "Main Street Gardens" (Main Street), Manor Road, Mansfield Grove Road, Maple Street, Maplevale Drive, Maplevale Court, Marie Drive, Marie Street, Martha Street, Martin Road, Mary Street (Box 565)